<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>WebDev on sbondLog</title>
    <link>https://log.sbond.ml/categories/webdev/</link>
    <description>Recent content in WebDev on sbondLog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 11:54:23 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://log.sbond.ml/categories/webdev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Keyframe Animations</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/css/keyframe-animations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 11:54:23 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/css/keyframe-animations/</guid>
      <description>IntroKeyframes in CSS are very diverse, you can use them for many things&amp;hellip; just get creative!
The BasicsThis is going to be the truly barebones version of what you can do with keyframes, but this is just an example which you should build on, on your own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change Subdomains Document Root In Apache Server</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/change-subdomains-documentroot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:52:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/change-subdomains-documentroot/</guid>
      <description>Step 1 - Create SubdomainIf you don&amp;rsquo;t have a subdomain on your apache server, you can follow this tutorial first and then come back.
Change Document RootIn &amp;lsquo;httpd-vhosts.conf&amp;rsquo; change the &amp;lsquo;Document Root&amp;rsquo; for the correct subdomain.
Mine, after editing, looks like this:
&amp;lt;VirtualHost *:80&amp;gt; ServerName cd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Solve CSS Not Updating In Your Browser</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/updating-css-on-browser/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 01:57:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/updating-css-on-browser/</guid>
      <description>What?If you are having problems getting your browser to update CSS on your web page then this post will definitely help you. There are mainly two different methods I will be showing you.
Method 1 - Clearing CacheIf you press F12, you now be able to right click on the refresh button and click the last option which is Empty Cache &amp;amp; Hard Reload.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Subdomains on Apache/Xampp</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/make-subdomains-on-apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 23:14:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/make-subdomains-on-apache/</guid>
      <description>What?When I say &amp;lsquo;subdomain&amp;rsquo; I am talking about the part that comes before the actual domain.
So the subdomain in this URL log.sbond.ml is the part that says log.
You can use subdomains to redirect to a different server which can show different content, but in this post, you will learn how to make a subdomain redirect to a directory in your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Indexing on Your Site</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/remove-indexing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:34:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/remove-indexing/</guid>
      <description>What?If you go to your site and put a folder in the address bar instead of a file you will be greeted with folder indexing, which allows people to look at whatever is in that folder/directory. When allowed anyone can type in a &amp;lsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; folder into the address bar on your site and then be greeted with an easy way of seeing every folder and every file on your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Protect One File on Your Site</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/password-protect-one-file-on-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:27:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/password-protect-one-file-on-site/</guid>
      <description>What?Instead of protecting the whole directory on your site there is a way to protect individual files in that directory.
How?Before you start: Finish this tutorial here and then come back to complete this one
Ok, once you have finished the other tutorial you can simply add the following code around the code you already have inside of your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Protect A Directory on Your Site</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/password-protect-directory-on-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:19:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/password-protect-directory-on-site/</guid>
      <description>What Will You Be Using?To properly protect your directories/files on your public web server you will want to use back-end password protection. Front-end protecting with using things like JavaScript will not be very protecting of your files because, someone who goes on your page could simply click F12 and change your code, so they can type in a password they want it to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Subdomains Which Redirect to Directory with .htaccess</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/making-subdomains-which-redirect-to-directory-htaccess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:15:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/making-subdomains-which-redirect-to-directory-htaccess/</guid>
      <description>What?A subdomain looks something like this: wiki.sbond.ml
You will recognise one because it will have text before the actual domain, something like the www. you see before most sites. Luckily we have the .htaccess file because this all becomes a lot easier once you get into it.
How?1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making .htaccess And .htpassword</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/making-.htaccess-and.htpassword/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:11:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/making-.htaccess-and.htpassword/</guid>
      <description>How?One thing to note is that .htaccess files do not have a file type. So always make sure when you are making this file that there should never be a file extension beside it.
There are multiple ways of making this file and I&amp;rsquo;m going to be showing you two of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Directory of File Using PHP</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/finding-directory-of-file-using-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:08:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/webdev/finding-directory-of-file-using-php/</guid>
      <description>What?If you are using a hosting provider that doesn&amp;rsquo;t tell you exactly where the directory of your files are you are going to have to use other methods of finding this out. One of the methods which I think is the simplest is using a small PHP script which will tell you exactly where you file is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scale on Hover CSS</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/css/scale-on-hover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:27:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/css/scale-on-hover/</guid>
      <description>What Do You Mean?What I mean by &amp;lsquo;Scale On Hover&amp;rsquo; is that when you hover over an element on your page it will scale up. I like to use this when you have something that is clickable and you want to add some &amp;lsquo;smoothness&amp;rsquo; to it. It makes the whole page flow nicer if you use it correctly and you don&amp;rsquo;t go over the top with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide Scrollbar CSS</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/l/css/hide-scrollbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:24:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/l/css/hide-scrollbar/</guid>
      <description>What?If you have some elements on your page that are causing a scrollbar to appear, but you would prefer them not to you can use some easy code in CSS to stop it from happening.
You can use this trick on the specific tag or you can disable the scrollbar fully by putting it in the body tag.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>