<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Logs on sbondLog</title>
    <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Logs on sbondLog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 23:14:03 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://log.sbond.ml/log/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How To Make Subdomains on Apache/Xampp</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/make-subdomains-on-apache/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 23:14:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/make-subdomains-on-apache/</guid>
      <description>What Are You Talking About? When I say &amp;lsquo;subdomain&amp;rsquo; I am talking about the part that comes before the actual domain.
So the subdomain in this URL log.sbond.ml is the part that says log.
You can use subdomains to redirect to a different server which can show different content, but in this post, you will learn how to make a subdomain redirect to a directory in your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove Indexing on Your Site</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/remove-indexing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:34:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/remove-indexing/</guid>
      <description>What? If you go to your site and put a folder in the address bar instead of a file you will be greeted with folder indexing, which allows people to look at whatever is in that folder/directory. When allowed anyone can type in a &amp;lsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; folder into the address bar on your site and then be greeted with an easy way of seeing every folder and every file on your site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Protect One File on Your Site</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/password-protect-one-file-on-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:27:51 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/password-protect-one-file-on-site/</guid>
      <description>What? Instead of protecting the whole directory on your site there is a way to protect individual files in that directory.
How? Before you start: Finish this tutorial here and then come back to complete this one
Ok, once you have finished the other tutorial you can simply add the following code around the code you already have inside of your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Password Protect A Directory on Your Site</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/password-protect-directory-on-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:19:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/password-protect-directory-on-site/</guid>
      <description>What Will You Be Using? To properly protect your directories/files on your public web server you will want to use back-end password protection. Front-end protecting with using things like JavaScript will not be very protecting of your files because, someone who goes on your page could simply click F12 and change your code, so they can type in a password they want it to be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Subdomains Which Redirect to Directory with .htaccess</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/making-subdomains-which-redirect-to-directory-htaccess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:15:10 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/making-subdomains-which-redirect-to-directory-htaccess/</guid>
      <description>What? A subdomain looks something like this: wiki.sbond.ml
You will recognise one because it will have text before the actual domain, something like the www. you see before most sites. Luckily we have the .htaccess file because this all becomes a lot easier once you get into it.
How? 1.Make sure you have made your .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making .htaccess And .htpassword</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/making-.htaccess-and.htpassword/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:11:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/making-.htaccess-and.htpassword/</guid>
      <description>How? One thing to note is that .htaccess files do not have a file type. So always make sure when you are making this file that there should never be a file extension beside it.
There are multiple ways of making this file and I&amp;rsquo;m going to be showing you two of them.
Way 1 In the first way, you can simply create a text document, open it up with any text editor then go to file &amp;gt;&amp;gt; Save as.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finding Directory of File Using PHP</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/finding-directory-of-file-using-php/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:08:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/webdev/finding-directory-of-file-using-php/</guid>
      <description>What? If you are using a hosting provider that doesn&amp;rsquo;t tell you exactly where the directory of your files are you are going to have to use other methods of finding this out. One of the methods which I think is the simplest is using a small PHP script which will tell you exactly where you file is.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple Calculator Python</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/python/simple-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 10:03:37 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/python/simple-calculator/</guid>
      <description>What? This simple calculator program will allow the user to enter two ( or more if you wish ) numbers and then choose a method to use (+, -, /, *). We will use if statements.
How? Well, first we need to add 3 ( or more ) variables. The first two will be holding the user&amp;rsquo;s numbers and the third will be the method they want to use ( Both variables will be asking for the user&amp;rsquo;s input as well ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Click Refresh Javascript</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/javascript/on-click-refresh-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:58:24 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/javascript/on-click-refresh-javascript/</guid>
      <description>What? If you have been looking to refresh the page with Javascript, you are lucky. I have three different methods of achieving this, with the last two being pretty similar. I am going to make an image on my page (You can use anything such as text or a button) and then add the onclick function to it, so when it is clicked it refreshes the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rockyou.txt</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/interesting/rockyou.txt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:55:52 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/interesting/rockyou.txt/</guid>
      <description> What&amp;rsquo;s this? Rockyou.txt is a text document filled with over 14 million cracked passwords. It is filled with easily crackable passwords.
Repo </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting your Hugo Site</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/hugo/host-hugo-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:48:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/hugo/host-hugo-site/</guid>
      <description>What? Hugo is a static site generator which can be used to make fast, accessible and overall fast web pages.
This page will show you how to get your Hugo site up and running either on a web server of yours or on Github pages.
How? First Steps 1. Fully delete the public folder inside of your Hugo site.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Suddenly Not Seeing Shared Devices On Network Win10</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/configuration/not-seeing-shared-devices-anymore-win10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:43:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/configuration/not-seeing-shared-devices-anymore-win10/</guid>
      <description>What? As you may know, Homegroup was removed from Windows 10 and the new Network tab replaced it. It is essentially the same thing, you can share files between different PCs across your network. I use this tool a lot when sharing files between PCs and it is very useful, whilst working.
If you have suddenly had your network tab stop showing certain PCs on your network consider this fix</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remove all Empty Lines Notepad&#43;&#43;</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/configuration/remove-empty-lines-notepad&#43;&#43;/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:41:02 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/configuration/remove-empty-lines-notepad&#43;&#43;/</guid>
      <description>What? If you have thousands or maybe just hundreds of empty lines in a text document you have, you may want to know how to remove all of the empty lines without having to manually do it.
To be clear I have used this in Notepad++, I am not sure if it would work anywhere else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In-Build Windows Screenshot Tool</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/configuration/in-build-screenshot-tool-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:38:03 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/configuration/in-build-screenshot-tool-windows/</guid>
      <description>What? Everyone knows about the old Snipping Tool that may have been used to screenshot certain things, to share or put in documents. There is now an easier to access tool which allows you to take screenshots quickly and then have them in your clipboard to paste somewhere.
It is honestly kind of a shame they didn&amp;rsquo;t add more features to the new screenshotting tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Add &#39;Open Command Window Here&#39; to Context Menu</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/configuration/add-open-command-window-here-to-the-context-menu/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:30:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/configuration/add-open-command-window-here-to-the-context-menu/</guid>
      <description>What? When you Shift + Right Click on a folder you get to see more options. Normally without any configuration, you only see the Open PowerShell Window Here. If you follow the steps below you will learn how to add the Open Command Window Here option to the context menu.
How?  Open Run by searching it on the start menu or pressing ⊞ Win Key + R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scale on Hover CSS</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/css/scale-on-hover/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:27:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/css/scale-on-hover/</guid>
      <description>What do I mean? What I mean by &amp;lsquo;Scale On Hover&amp;rsquo; is that when you hover over an element on your page it will scale up. I like to use this when you have something that is clickable and you want to add some &amp;lsquo;smoothness&amp;rsquo; to it. It makes the whole page flow nicer if you use it correctly and you don&amp;rsquo;t go over the top with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hide Scrollbar CSS</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/css/hide-scrollbar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 09:24:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/css/hide-scrollbar/</guid>
      <description>What? If you have some elements on your page that are causing a scrollbar to appear, but you would prefer them not to you can use some easy code in CSS to stop it from happening.
You can use this trick on the specific tag or you can disable the scrollbar fully by putting it in the body tag.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun Commands</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3/fun-commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 09:01:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3/fun-commands/</guid>
      <description>How to use First, you will need to be the Admin/Host of the mission you are playing. To execute the commands you will need to click ESC and then type the commands into the Debug Console. You can click Local to execute the code locally ( Just For You ), Server will execute the code to the server and Global will execute the code globally ( to everyone ).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teleporting</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/teleporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2018 08:55:21 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/teleporting/</guid>
      <description>Teleporting to markers To teleport players to markers we will be making use of both setPos &amp;amp; getMarkerPos.
First, we will have to place a marker down in the spot we want the players to be teleported to. You can do this in the ArmA 3DEN Editor, by going to Markers (F6), Icons and then selecting the marker you want to place down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple While Loops</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/simple-while-loops/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Nov 2018 08:53:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/simple-while-loops/</guid>
      <description>While Loops?? If you ever want to create a loop for whatever reason you can do it easily with while loops.
How do I use them? If you wanted to create a hint every 15 seconds you could very easily execute this script once and have it do the rest of the work for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Show Dialog &amp; Let Players Move</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/show-dialog-whilst-letting-players-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Nov 2018 08:30:50 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/show-dialog-whilst-letting-players-move/</guid>
      <description>What are you talking about? There is a way to show dialogs differently so that the player can retain his control over moving his character. The player can move around, but there will still be a mouse pointer on the screen allowing them to select what they need to. This can be useful in many ways in many different situations you may have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Removing or Adding Items</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/removing-or-adding-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Oct 2018 08:24:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/removing-or-adding-items/</guid>
      <description>Adding Items You can use the commands below to start adding Items to players. Of course, you can change &amp;lsquo;player&amp;rsquo; to whatever you want as long as you define it first.
Inside of the Speech Marks, you will put classnames for the items you want to be added to the player.
 player addHeadgear &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placing Trees in Eden Editor</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/placing-trees-in-eden-editor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 07:47:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/placing-trees-in-eden-editor/</guid>
      <description>How would I do this? To add a tree you first have to place down a game logic wherever you please and copy the code below into it: _tree = createSimpleObject [&amp;ldquo;TREE NAME&amp;rdquo;, [X,Y,Z]];
Once you have the code in there you are going to have to edit some things before your tree will be placed:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi Line Text in Dialogs</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/multi-line-text-in-dialogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 07:44:19 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/multi-line-text-in-dialogs/</guid>
      <description>What mate? If you are creating a dialog and need to have a long line of text and it doesn&amp;rsquo;t fit in your dialog frame, you are going to be happy to know that there is a style you can use to make your text go into multiple lines.
How? In your dialog just add the following lines of code:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ArmA Dialog Creator</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/arma-dialog-creator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Oct 2018 05:37:26 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/arma-dialog-creator/</guid>
      <description>What Is This? ArmA Dialog Creator is an amazing tool created by Kayler Renslow. It is the easy way of creating functional dialogs in ArmA 3. You can simply download it from his Github and install it. Once you have done that you are ready to start creating dialogs the easy way!
How To Start Once you have opened the .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hints</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/hints/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Oct 2018 07:29:31 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/hints/</guid>
      <description>What is this? Hints are something you can use very easily to alert players of something or tell them what they have to do next or what they have done. It basically gives the players or whoever you let see the hint a little box with text inside of it.
They are very useful in a lot of cases and are super easy to use!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>execVM Loops</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/execvm-loops/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 07:24:40 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/execvm-loops/</guid>
      <description>Why do it like this? You can use execVM to loop one script over an over again, but you can&amp;rsquo;t stop it once it has started. It is great when you have a script you want to run every x seconds for the whole mission. It is also really simple so it is more appealing over other ways of creating a loop because it requires almost no effort.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advanced Holstering</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/advanced-holstering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Oct 2018 05:02:44 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/advanced-holstering/</guid>
      <description>What Is This? Believe it or not there is a very easy way to allow your character to put their primary weapon on their back and or pistol in their holster. This will work great in scenes you want to have a great cinematic effect. This will work wherever you put it and is a great line of code to have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>execVM</title>
      <link>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/execvm/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 03:52:05 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://log.sbond.ml/log/arma3-mission-editing/execvm/</guid>
      <description> What Is execVM? execVM is an essential command for ArmA 3 scripting. It allows you to call a script at any point.
Example execVM is really easy to use and is used like such:
execVM &#34;nameOfScript.filetype&#34;; </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>